export const data = [
  // {
  //   question: "1. What does HTML stand for?",
  //   option1: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
  //   option2: "High Tech Modern Language",
  //   option3: "Hyper Transfer Main Link",
  //   option4: "Home Tool Markup Language",
  //   answer: "option1"
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "2. Which one is the capital of Pakistan?",
  //   option1: "Karachi",
  //   option2: "Lahore",
  //   option3: "Islamabad",
  //   option4: "Peshawar",
  //   answer: "option3"
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "3. What is the result of 5 + 7 * 2?",
  //   option1: "24",
  //   option2: "19",
  //   option3: "26",
  //   option4: "17",
  //   answer: "option2"
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "4. Who developed the theory of relativity?",
  //   option1: "Isaac Newton",
  //   option2: "Albert Einstein",
  //   option3: "Nikola Tesla",
  //   option4: "Galileo Galilei",
  //   answer: "option2"
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "5. Which language is mainly used for Android app development?",
  //   option1: "Python",
  //   option2: "Java",
  //   option3: "C#",
  //   option4: "Swift",
  //   answer: "option2"
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "6. What is the chemical symbol for Gold?",
  //   option1: "Ag",
  //   option2: "Au",
  //   option3: "Gd",
  //   option4: "Go",
  //   answer: "option2"
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "7. Which planet is called the Red Planet?",
  //   option1: "Venus",
  //   option2: "Jupiter",
  //   option3: "Mars",
  //   option4: "Saturn",
  //   answer: "option3"
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "8. Which data structure uses FIFO (First In First Out)?",
  //   option1: "Stack",
  //   option2: "Queue",
  //   option3: "Array",
  //   option4: "Tree",
  //   answer: "option2"
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "9. Who is known as the Father of Computers?",
  //   option1: "Charles Babbage",
  //   option2: "Alan Turing",
  //   option3: "Bill Gates",
  //   option4: "Steve Jobs",
  //   answer: "option1"
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "10. Which of the following is NOT a programming language?",
  //   option1: "Python",
  //   option2: "C++",
  //   option3: "HTML",
  //   option4: "JavaScript",
  //   answer: "option3"
  // }
];

